fbtz.com 2007-12-17

# Privacy Policy

_Privacy Policy_

fbtz.com like a lot of other websites makes use of various technologies to improve functionality and performance for its users. These technologies include the use of cookies and tracking IP addresses. 

**Cookies**  
fbtz.com makes use of cookies throughout the website. The information supplied by cookies allows us to deliver specific content to individual users and keep track of their activity. Cookies are used in such things as the polls on fbtz.com and the community forums. 

**Personal Information**  
fbtz.com does not collect personal information such as real names, addresses or phone numbers. Visitors wishing to contribute to community features such as chat and forums provide details such as their email address and ICQ numbers when they signup. These members also have the option to keep these details private, so they will only be visible to fbtz.com staff. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. fbtz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Statistics**  
fbtz.com tracks and records IP addresses and what websites/search engines users have entered the site through for statistical purposes. These statistics help us improve functionality and performance for our users. 

**Community**  
The community section of this site makes use of chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Third Parties**  
Any information fbtz.com may obtain from its users is not sold or provided to third parties or other companies, nor will it ever be.
